// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which is the brightest planet in the night's sky?",
    answer: "Venus",
    options: [
      "Jupiter",
      "Venus",
      "Mercury",
      "Saturn"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which is the second smallest planet within our solar system?",
    answer: "Mars",
    options: [
      "Mars",
      "Venus",
      "Mercury",
      "Pluto"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The moon called Titan orbits whuich planet?",
    answer: "Saturn",
    options: [
      "Jupiter",
      "Uranus",
      "Neptune",
      "Saturn"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Uranus has only been visited by what spacecraft?",
    answer: "Voyager 2",
    options: [
      "Mariner 4",
      "Apollo 11",
      "Cassini",
      "Voyager 2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many of our planets can be seen without a telescope?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "7",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the sun mainly made from?",
    answer: "Gas",
    options: [
      "Liquid lava",
      "Rock",
      "Molten iron",
      "Gas"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which planet do the moons Oberon and Titania belong to?",
    answer: "Uranus",
    options: [
      "Earth",
      "Neptune",
      "Uranus",
      "Saturn"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which planet takes 165 years to orbit the Sun?",
    answer: "Neptune",
    options: [
      "Uranus",
      "Neptune",
      "Jupiter",
      "Saturn"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which planet is also known as The Evening Star?",
    answer: "Venus",
    options: [
      "Mars",
      "Mercury",
      "Jupiter",
      "Venus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which planet has the Borealis Basin?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "Mercury",
      "Mars",
      "Venus",
      "Earth"
    ]
  },
];
